<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-04-12T19:01:49-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Yong’s Blog</title><subtitle>An engineer in search of meaning in life</subtitle><author><name>Yongkyun Shin</name><email>yongkyuns@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">How To Gradually Convince Your Team For A Change</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/How-to-gradually-convince-your-team-for-a-change/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How To Gradually Convince Your Team For A Change" /><published>2022-04-12T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2022-04-12T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/How-to-gradually-convince-your-team-for-a-change</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/How-to-gradually-convince-your-team-for-a-change/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/change.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Change is inevitable for an organization to grow and evolve.
If an organization does not change much, there is a good 
chance that your organization is dysfunctional or unable to
improve. However, change is also intrusive and uncomfortable by nature. 
When stakes are high, the most natural thing to do for leaders
is to stick to the methods that have worked in the past. As it is
often said, “If it ain’t broken, don’t fix it!” In some cases,
proposing a change can initially bring visibly negative impacts to 
the very problem that you are trying to solve by those changes. 
So how do we gracefully introduce a change to an engineering team,
when you know your ability to propose that change is somewhat limited?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I faced this challenge when proposing to migrate a unit test framework
within my team. Changes in tooling may seem trivial for some, but when
you are designing safety-critical, high-volume production software, any
small change in the infrastructure can lead to highly undesirable 
sequence of headaches. More importantly, switching the framework
meant throwing out at least some of the existing tests and having 
to rewrite them, while learning how to use it!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Yongkyun Shin</name><email>yongkyuns@gmail.com</email></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Starting Blog: A Learning Journal</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Starting-blog-A-Learning-Journal/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Starting Blog: A Learning Journal" /><published>2022-04-09T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2022-04-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Starting-blog:-A-Learning-Journal</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Starting-blog-A-Learning-Journal/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/1.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, I was going through lots of thoughts on what I would like 
to work on for the next 5 to 10 years, and began to realize a few things.
Growing up, I was never the type of kid to keep a good record of my 
thoughts and ideas. In a sense, I liked the volatility of thoughts as they
flow through my mind and sometimes disappear out of thin air. Most 
would still stick around, so I didn’t really have an issue. But as 
I got older and began to work more and more with other people,
I realized that keeping records of my thoughts can be beneficial.
It could help me organize my thoughts, but also help me reflect on 
it from a third person’s perspective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I decided to try and write blogs on some of the more lingering
thoughts I have on engineering and life in general. 
I am hoping that it would help me reflect on my journey when I look 
back in 15 to 20 years. So, onwards with the learning journal!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Yongkyun Shin</name><email>yongkyuns@gmail.com</email></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>